Mel Brooks

Full Stack Developer

linkedin.com/in/melbcoding github.com/melbcoding melbcoding@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Full stack developer with 2+ years working in the web development industry. Fluent in Python and Javascript with experience building consumer facing products using a variety of technologies depending on the client's need. Strong collaboration and communication skills with the ability to learn new technologies quickly and adapt with the ever evolving landscape that is web development by writing and maintaining code by keeping the industry's best practices in mind.

SKILLS

Python, SQL, Flask, Django, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React API,

Git, wireframing, UI & UX design, Database Design, Object Oriented Programming (OOP), Restful Routing, testing and debugging, Amazon Web Services (AWS)

EXPERIENCE

Coding Dojo, Online - Web Development Instructor

April 2021 - PRESENT

- Prepare learning material and group activities
- Present curriculum and demo code live while cultivating a fertile learning experience
- Review student assignments and connecting with at risk students to nudge them back on track- student success is the primary objective

Mel Brooks Creative, Los Angeles, CA - Owner

July 2013 - Present

- Illustration, design and/or copyright services
- Notable Clients: Coffee Manufactory, Verve, Tigermoth Goods

EDUCATION

Coding Dojo- Certification in Fullstack Python and Javascript

October 2020 - April 2021

- Python + Django ORM & Flask Framework, SQL, MySQL
- Javascript + React, Node, Express, MongoDB